S Phanider

Graphic Designer

About me.

Ability to create effective and innovtive designs to convey the desired ideas. Experienced in Content Specialis Graphic Design and video editing's. I hold 4 years of experience in graphic design Enthusiasm and passionate towards design, and accept difficulties as challenges.

Intrests





Traveling

Music

Contact: +91-6281592098

GMail: Praj18647@gmail.com

Portfolio link

https://drive.google.com/drive /folders/1Q3v_-VGkM0Yv2aUadBiqj cv51gAe9YUQ?usp=sharing



EXPERIENCE

Regalix Inc.

Data Visualization Analyst (Graphic) May 2021 - Jan-2021

Sumtotal Systems India Private Limited

Content Specialist Graphic Designer

May 2019 - Dec 2020

Info E-Search

Closed Captioning

April 2017 - September 2017

Sam-Tech Services

Graphic Designer

February 2015 - March 2017



EDUCATION

Arena Multimedia

Graphic Designing / UI Front-End Developer

2018 - 2019

Board of Intermediate

New Era Junior College

2011 - 2013

Board of Secondary Education

Mother Theresa High School

2010



APPLICATIONS

Adobe Illustrator
Adobe Photoshop
Adobe After Effects
Adobe Premiere

Adobe InDesign
PPT Presentations



SKILLS

User Interface Design Graphic Design Post Production Icon Design Logo Design Banners / Posts